aceinfowayindia.com 2014-02-09

# Ace Infoway India-Privacy Policy

Ace Infoway India very strongly believes in it’s Privacy Policy. This privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

###### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

###### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you. 
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

###### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.   

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

### Services include:

  * Web design & development
  * Graphic design
  * Application development &       programming
  * Web hosting & maintenance
  * Domain Registration
  * SEO & SEM
  * Consulting & training

### Our standard web solution include:

  * Creative analysis and planning
  * Choose from 2 visual concepts
  * Website built in valid CSS /       XHTML
  * Tested in all browsers
  * Domain Registration
  * Powerful content management       system
  * News article system with RSS       support
  * Basic Search Engine       Optimization

### How we work...
